Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm Microfilm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- 16mm Investigations, 1913-1950 and undated
  - Shell Oil Co.
    - Shell vol. 7
      - Letter on information of the ration of cars to families by income groups, 1937 July
      - Information on Flivver aeroplanes, 1937 Aug.
      - Gasoline and oil advertising, 1937 Aug.
      - Shell specialties, 1937 Nov.
      - Study of motor oil consumption (no report submitted), 1938 Jan.
      - Plan for testing furniture polish, 1938 Mar.
      - Window cleaning fluids, 1938 Mar.
      - Sales and net earnings of oil companies 1936-1937, 1938 Mar.
      - An estimate of the market for anti-freeze, 1938 Apr.
      - Shell furniture polish test, 1938 May
      - Shell specialty products (insect spray, window cleaner)--Name survey, 1938 July
    - Shell vol. 8
      - Analysis of car ownership and gasoline and oil expenditures, by family income groups, 1938 Sept.
      - Gasoline and motor oil sales 1938 Jan.-Dec., 1938 Oct.
      - Shell consumer motor oil movie test (Also Crossley inv.), 1939 Jan.
      - Statistics on women drivers, 1939 Feb.
      - Gasoline and motor oil sales 1939 Jan.-Dec., 1939 Mar.
      - Shell Oil U.S. territory passenger car registrations, 1937, 1939 Mar.
      - Two gasoline buying habits of Good Housekeeping readers, 1939 Mar. and Oct., 1939 Dec.
  - J.B. Williams Co.
    - J.B. Williams vol. 4
      - Barber shop survey in 9 larger cities and 18 small cities, 1937 Oct. (Reel 415)
      - Office investigation on talcum powder, 1937 Oct.
      - Tables--A suggested change of sales territories like jobbing areas, 1937 Nov.
      - Shaving cream cap designs, 1937 Nov.
      - Charts of sales, 1926-1936, 1937 Nov.
      - Distribution and relative sale strength of 10 cent size shaving items among wholesalers and retailers, 1938 Jan.
      - Barber shop and supply house investigation in N.Y. City and Youngstown, Ohio, 1938 Jan.
      - Test of names for new Williams talc, 1938 Jan.
      - Test of 2 formulae of brushless shaving cream, 1938 Jan.
      - Sales of shaving preparation holiday sets, 1938 Feb.
      - Survey of men's preferences for selected toilet soap colors, 1938 Mar.
      - Survey on use of Castile soap in the home, 1938 Apr.
      - Name for Williams talcum powder, 1938 May
    - J.B. Williams vol. 5
      - Electric razor survey, 1938 May
      - 6 office investigation on men's shampoo habits, 1938 June
      - WTIC dollar sales, 1938 June
      - Men's bath soaps (San Francisco Office), 1938 July
      - Report on use of cigarette stain remover, 1938 July
      - Memo on Williams hospital massage talc, 1938 Aug.
      - Postcard survey among men requesting Glider samples, spring 1938, 1938 Aug.
      - Relative popularity of 5-blade and 10-blade packages of razor blades, 1938 Sept.
      - Toilet articles for men sold in department stores, 1938 Sept.
      - Dog soap investigation, 1938 Oct.
      - Sales and moving average of Williams' products, 1938 Oct.
      - Annual Aqua Velva sales in ounces, 1938 Nov.
      - Second postcard survey among men requesting Glider samples, Nov. 1938, 1938 Dec.
      - Report on test of after shaving cold cream, 1939 Jan.
      - Estimated domestic monthly net sales--In dollars, by products, 1935-1939, 1939 Mar.
      - Survey among drug store displays, 1939 June
      - Third postcard survey among men requesting Glider samples, May 1939, 1939 July
  - Peter's Milk Chocolate
    - Account history, 1919 (Reel 427)
  - Kellogg (Australia)
    - Advertising recommendations for Jan.-Dec., 1942 Dec.
    - Dog food investigation, 1942 Jan.
  - Florida Citrus Industry
    - Committee report, 1935 Oct. 3
    - Report, 1941 Apr.
  - Standard Brands, Inc. (Mr. Bailey's files)
    - The chemistry of tea, 1923 June
    - Tea manufacture, 1938 Oct. 31
    - Science studies claims for tea (Dr. Eddy), 1938 June
    - Report on beneficial effect of fresh coffee, circa 1938
    - The chemistry of coffee (P.W. Punnett and W.H. Eddy), circa 1938
    - Production of aldehydes in the oil of coffee, circa 1938
    - Coffee aroma, 1931 Nov.
    - Study of oils and fats extracted from coffee, 1933 Apr. 15
    - Plan for increasing coffee consumption in the U.S., 1934 July
    - Progressive grocer pamphlets, undated
    - Coffee market--Evaluating it, undated
    - Trends in sales of household coffee makers--Regular coffee (McCall's Marketing Research Dept.), undated
    - American home survey on how people make coffee (John Felix associates), 1940s
    - Couponing and sampling (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 Apr.
    - Home preparation of coffee (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 Apr.
    - Why less purchasing of Chase & Sanborn (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 Apr.
    - Albany survey instant Tender Leaf Tea (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 Oct.
    - Joplin, Mo. survey of Chase & Sanborn (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 Oct.
    - Chase & Sanborn coffee and instant--Coupon (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 Oct.
    - Consumer attitude--Instant tea (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 Oct.
    - 2nd study of consumer attitude of Chase & Sanborn coffee (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1949 Apr.
    - Extracts from advertising talk by Hardley H. Noyes, 1949
    - Listing of Standard Brands products (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 May
    - Consumer test of Chase & Sanborn coffee vs. Folgers's (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 Aug.
    - Fleischmann's yeast in Philadelphia (Market Research Dept. pamphlet), 1948 Aug.
    - Coffee--Consumer Panel special analysis, 1948 June
    - Supplement to Chase & Sanborn advertising plans, 1948 July
    - Recommendations on Chase & Sanborn coffee for fall of 1948, 1948 July
    - Media recommendations on Chase & Sanborn coffee for 1949, 1948 Nov.
    - Chase & Sanborn advertising plans for 1948-1949, 1948 Nov.
    - Coffee test by National Family Opinion Nov.-Dec., 1949 Jan.
    - National survey of coffee by M.F. Hanson for JWT, 1949 Jan.
    - Instant Chase & Sanborn coffee 1949 sales strategy, 1949 Jan.
    - Instant Chase & Sanborn coffee regional managers meeting, 1949 Jan.
    - Outline of discussion of Chase & Sanborn at regional managers meeting, 1949 Jan.
    - 8 oz. instant Chase & Sanborn--Introduction, sales plans--Pacific region, 1949 Jan.
    - Presentation--Chase & Sanborn coffee, 1949 Feb.
    - Instant Chase & Sanborn--Grocery division sales meeting, 1949 Feb.
    - Organization meetings, 1949 Mar.
    - Dallas district sales meeting, 1949 Mar.
    - Chase & Sanborn coffee copy platform, 1949 May
  - J.B. Williams Co.
    - J.B. Williams vol. 6
      - Dealer survey on J.B. Williams Christmas sets, 1939 Dec.
      - Fourth postcard survey among men requesting Glider samples, 1939 Dec.
      - Fifth postcard survey among men requesting Glider samples, 1940 Apr.
      - Postcard survey among men and women requesting true & false games and books, 1940 Apr.
      - Survey of proposed offer of life with father by JBW, 1940 Apr.
      - Postcard survey among men who purchased Roto-Shavers, 1940 May
      - Shaving bowl survey among department store buyers in N.Y., Chicago and San Francisco, 1940 June
      - Postcard survey among members of the Appalachian Club, 1940 June
      - Survey among department store buyers of men's deodorants, 1940 June
      - Test of 3 glass containers, 1940 Aug.
      - Information on Gillette deal, 1940 Oct.
      - Consumer sales on lather cream, brushless cream and lotion in Rochester and Providence, 1940 Nov.
      - Sixth postcard survey among men requesting Glider samples, 1940 Dec.
      - Office investigation on Williams' talcum container, 1940 Nov.
    - J.B. Williams vol. 7
      - Williams department store survey on Christmas packages, 1941 Jan.
      - Postcard survey among purchasers of 'Lectric Shave, Aqua Velva, 1941 Jan.
      - Office survey on lanolin oil, 1941 Mar.
      - Dealer survey in 4 cities, 1941 Apr.
      - Test of Rayex hair dressing, 1941 Apr.
      - Office survey on the carrying of keys, 1941 Apr.
      - Baby soap headline appeal, 1941 May
      - Postcard survey among owners of Williams Roto-Shaver, 1941 June
      - Test of new Williams Rayex, 1941 July
      - Information on army, Navy and Marines shaving kits, 1941 Oct.
      - Shaving cream investigation among dermatologists, Oct., 1941 Nov.
      - Shaving cream investigation among dermatologists, Nov., 1941 Dec.
      - Postcard survey among owners of electric shavers, 1941 Dec.
      - Barber shop survey, 1941 Dec.
      - Drug and department store survey--Christmas shaving sets, 1941 Dec.
      - Distribution study of shaving mugs and bowls, 1941 Dec.
      - Office test of Rayex, 1942 Jan.
  - Lever Brothers
    - Account history (Continued on reel 444), 1916-1927 (Reel 443)
    - Account history, 1916-1927 (Reel 444)
  - Eastman Kodak
    - Eastman display check in N.Y. and Chicago, 1933 Dec.
    - Dealer investigation of movie cameras, 1934 May
    - Display in Liggett store in N.Y. and Chicago, 1934 June
    - Consumer radio test investigation in Detroit, 1934 Sept.
    - Window display check, 1934 Dec.
    - Film displays at Macy's, 1935 Aug.
    - Seven interviews with firms on their opinion of the Sales Analysis Institute course, 1938 May
    - Total advertising expenditures, 1939 Jan.
    - Special tabulation made from Roper's big business survey, 1939 June
    - Trends in advertising illustrations 1935-1940, 1940 Oct.
    - Survey among doctors, 1940 Nov.
  - General Electric
    - Panel home survey--Refrigerators, undated
    - Panel home survey--Kitchen ranges, undated
    - Panel home survey--Washing machines, undated
    - Panel home survey--Vacuum cleaners, undated
    - Panel home survey--Electric irons, undated
    - Panel home survey--Electric toasters, undated
    - Panel home survey--Electric mixers, undated
    - Panel home survey--Electric clocks, undated
    - Panel home survey--Electric home freezers, undated
    - Panel home survey--Electric ironers, undated
    - Panel home survey--Room coolers, undated
    - Panel home survey--Disposals, undated
    - Panel home survey--Dishwashers, undated
    - Panel home survey--Automatic blankets, undated
    - Panel home survey--Clothes dryers, undated
    - Panel home survey--Silex coffee makers, undated
    - Panel home survey--Leading brands of washing machines, undated
  - Johns-Manville
    - Johns-Manville vol. 3
      - Study of overhead door market, 1936 Apr.
      - Study of paint industry, 1936 Apr.
      - Paint survey among building supply dealers, 1936 June
      - Survey of cedar grain siding shingles in Chicago, 1936 June
      - Model home investigation, 1936 Aug.
      - Survey on kitchens, bathrooms, attics and basements, 1936 Oct.
      - Information on 18 large corporations, 1937 May
      - Ways of spending $250.00, 1938 July
      - Response to building materials promotions, by month, 1938 Oct.
    - Johns-Manville vol. 4
      - Survey on sand urns, 1939 Apr.
      - Preliminary home insulation survey, 1939 Apr.
      - Preliminary home insulation survey, 1939 May
      - Test survey on building materials--Dealers, 1939 Sept.
      - Test survey on building materials--Dealers--Revised to combine all brands of each manufacturer, 1939 Sept.
      - Readership ratings of ads in the Saturday Evening Post, 1941 Nov.
      - Readership ratings of ads in the Saturday Evening Post, Nov. 15, 1941 Dec.
  - Life Insurance
    - Life Insurance vol. 1
      - Office surveys on life insurance companies--4 cities, 1939 July, Sept.
      - Surveys on life insurance companies--23 cities (Not delivered), 1939 Oct.
      - Public attitude survey in 14 cities part I, 1940 June
      - Elmo Roper--Survey designed to measure effectiveness of insurance publicity--Report 1, 1940 June
      - Elmo Roper--Survey designed to measure effectiveness of insurance publicity--Report 2, 1940 Nov.
      - Elmo Roper--Some comparative insurance tabulations, regrouped, 1941 Jan.
      - Dr. Lucas--Measurement of attitude changes caused by film shown, 1942 Jan.
      - New York Office survey on life insurance, 1942 Oct.
      - New York Office survey on attitude toward government health problems, 1942 Dec.
    - Life Insurance vol. 2
      - Public attitude toward the Four Freedoms, 1943 June
      - 1st installment survey on Freedom from Want--Elmo Roper report, 1943 Apr.
      - Memo to H. Flower re: insurance survey among editors of daily newspapers, 1944 Jan.
      - Measurement of attitudes toward and knowledge of certain aspects of life insurance companies--Steamship lines--Elmo Roper report, 1944 Feb.
      - Public attitude toward the Four Freedoms, 1944 Mar.
      - A philosophy of spending, prepared by Claire Wilcox, 1944 Sept.
      - Survey in New York Office of JWT on life insurance agents' service, 1948 Feb.
      - Survey in New York Office of JWT on knowledge of insurance terms used in advertising, 1948 Nov.
  - Sharp & Dohme
    - Office survey on Sucrets, 1944 July
    - Antiseptics--Consumer Panel survey, 1945 Mar.
    - Cough drops/Lozenges--Consumer Panel survey, 1945 Mar.
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
    - Chase & Sanborn vol. 20
      - Spot radio test, Oct.-Nov. 1940, 1941 Jan.
      - Coupon test, Hartford, Feb.-Nov. 1940, 1941 Jan.
      - Special local activity cities, Apr.-Nov. 1940, 1941 Jan.
      - Special local activity cities, Apr.-Dec. 1940, 1941 Feb.
      - Spot radio test, Oct.-Nov. 1940, 1941 Feb.
      - Pittsburgh coupon test, May-Dec. 1940, 1941 Feb.
      - Des Moines coupon test, Apr.-Dec. 1940, 1941 Feb.
      - Local activity cities, additional, 1941 Feb.
      - Hartford coupon test, Feb.-Dec. 1940, 1941 Feb.
      - Test of Fleischmann soluble coffee vs. Geo. Washington coffee, 1941 Feb.
      - Coffee taste test--Control 130 and 115, N.Y. and Chicago Offices, 1941 Mar.
      - Springtime and harvest #1, Sept. 1939-Aug. 1940, 1941 Mar.
      - Springtime and harvest #2, Apr.-Aug. 1940, 1941 Mar.
    - Chase & Sanborn vol. 21
      - Intensive dealer and consumer survey in Nashville, Tenn., 1941 Apr.
      - Special local activity cities, Jan., 1941 Apr.
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-Additional, 1941 Apr.
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-Feb., 1941 Apr.
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-Feb.-Additional, 1941 Apr.
      - Comparison Chase & Sanborn surveys--Hartford, Grand Rapids, Des Moines, Nashville, 1941 May
      - Chase & Sanborn Seal Brand coffee--Vacuum pack in Cook County, Jan.-Mar., 1941 May
      - Chase & Sanborn Seal Brand coffee--Vacuum pack in Cook County, May-Dec., 1941 May
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-Mar., 1941 May
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-Mar.-Additional, 1941 May
    - Chase & Sanborn vol. 22
      - New twin-pack consumer survey in Syracuse, Apr., 1941 May
      - Survey on preference of 3 Chase & Sanborn cans, 7 cities (See vol. 2 for final), 1941 May
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-Apr., 1941 June
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-Apr.--Additional, 1941 June
      - Test of spot radio in Rochester and Louisville, spring 1941, 1941 July
      - Test of day time radio in N.Y. City, spring 1941, 1941 July
      - Vacuum pack in Cook County, Jan.-May, 1941 July
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-May, 1941 July
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-May-Additional, 1941 July
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-June, 1941 Aug.
      - Special local activity cities, Jan.-June-Additional, 1941 Aug.
    - Chase & Sanborn vol. 23
      - N.Y. metropolitan markets, 1941 Aug.
      - Consumer test of preference for vacuum can designs, 1941 July
      - Vacuum pack in Cook County, Jan.-May, 1941 Aug.
      - Outdoor posting test in western cities, Apr.-June, 1941 Aug.
      - Outdoor panel test in Springfield, Mass., Feb.-May, 1941 Aug.
      - Outdoor panel test in Albany, N.Y., Feb.-May, 1941 Aug.
      - Spot radio test in Seattle, Mar.-June, 1941 Aug.
      - Vacuum pack newspaper test in Portland, Ore., Jan.-July, 1941 Aug.
      - Vacuum pack in Cook County, Jan.-July, 1941 Sept.
      - Results of coffee tests, 1941 Oct.
      - Vacuum pack in Cook County, Jan.-Aug., 1941 Oct.
      - Detroit distribution survey, 1941 Oct.
      - Trends in national consumer advertising, by media, 1941 Oct.
      - Outdoor posting test in western cities, Apr.-Sept., 1941 Oct.
      - Vacuum pack in Cook County, Jan.-Sept/, 1941 Nov.
      - Southwestern division posters, July-Oct., 1941 Nov.
      - Vacuum pack in Cook County, Jan.-Oct., 1941 Dec.
      - Outdoor posting test in Springfield, Mass., Feb.-Oct., 1941 Dec.
      - Outdoor posting test in Albany, N.Y., Feb.-Oct., 1941 Dec.
      - Brands of coffee in the home at present, 1941 Dec.
    - Fleischmann's Yeast vol. 25
      - Trend of foil sales, first 6 months, 1939 July
      - Fleischmann's Forvitan--Consumer test, Morristown, N.J., 1939 Aug.
      - Ironized yeast--Chain store sales, 1939 Aug.
      - Fleischmann's foil yeast sales, first 9 months, 1939 Nov.
      - Fleischmann's Forvitan--Taste test, 1939 Dec.
      - Fleischmann's Forvitan--Investigation in Portland Maine, 1939 Dec.
      - Memo on prices of cod liver oil, 1939 Dec.
      - Forvitan taste test, Long Island day school, 1940 Jan.
      - Estimated advertising cost for 1940 (Pieces and pound), 1940 Jan.
      - Memo on Mr. Snyder's analysis of radio vs. non-radio trend sales of foil yeast, 1940 Feb.
      - Financial reports International Vitamin Corp. and NW Yeast Co., 1940 Feb.
      - Confidential data on undergraduates weight at Yale University, 1940 Feb.
      - Forvitan taste test, orange flavor vs. regular, 1940 Mar.
      - Nation-wide yeast and vitamin survey and plan, 1940 Mar.
    - Fleischmann's Yeast vol. 26
      - Consumer survey on Forvitan in Harrisburg, Pa., 1940 Mar.
      - Mr. Frey's analysis of the Fleischmann foil yeast survey, 1940 May
      - Fleischmann's yeast for bread--Flour and bread consumption trends, 1940 May
      - Fleischmann's foil yeast--Test of radio spot announcements, 1940 May
    - Fleischmann's Yeast for Bakers vol. 1
      - Dealer and consumer bread survey in Green Bay, Wis., 1940 Nov.
      - Flour and bread consumption trends, 1941 Jan.
      - Fleischmann's yeast--Latin American, 1941 Oct.
  - Ward Baking Co.
    - Ward Baking vol. 1
      - Benefits from vitamins, 1941 Oct.
      - Consumer test of bread samples, #1--A, B, C, 1941 Oct.
      - Consumer test of bread samples, #2--Y, Z, 1941 Oct.
      - Dealer and consumer survey of N.Y. metro market on bread, 1941 Oct.
      - Leading bread and cake companies, 1941 Oct.
      - Consumer test of bread samples, #3--5 vs. 6, 5A vs. 6A, 1941 Oct.
      - Fleischmann's yeast for bread--Flour and bread consumption trends, 1940 May
      - Fleischmann's yeast for bread--Flour and bread consumption trends, 1941 Jan.
    - Ward Baking vol. 2
      - Vitamin and enriched bread surveys in Detroit and N.Y., 1941 Oct.
      - N.Y. consumer survey on enriched bread and vitamin knowledge, 1942 Mar.
      - Dealer survey in the N.Y. metro market, 1942 May
      - Consumer test of bread samples, #4 and #5, 1942 Sept.
      - Consumer test of bread samples, #14 and #15--Plan, 1942 Oct.
      - Consumer test of bread samples, first, nos. 3, 4, 5; second, nos. 14, 15, 16, 1942 Nov.
      - Article on price of bread, 1943 Feb.
      - Memo to Mr. O'Neill Ryan on population of N.Y., 1943 Apr.
      - Memo to John Hosch on trends in costs vs. bread prices, 1939-1943, 1943 July
      - Memo to John Hosch on trends in costs vs. bread prices, 1939-1943, 56 cities vs. 51 cities, 1943 July
  - American Home Products
    - Public relations survey and recommendations, 1943 (Reel 711)
  - Fred Astaire Dance Studio
    - Dance survey, 1943 Mar.
  - Market Research
    - Product test of coffee, 1948
    - Cross-Tabulations of coffee, 1949
  - Ballantine vol. 3
    - Ballantine's sales, Jan., 1941 Mar.
    - Retail price survey in N.Y. City, 1941 Mar.
    - Survey of beer and ale situation at University of Michigan, 1941 Jan.
    - Ballantine's sales, Mar., 1941 May
  - Standard Brands, Inc.
    - Chase & Sanborn vol. 24
      - Consumer survey on coffee containers, 1942 Jan.
      - Coffee tests, 1942 Jan.
      - Vacuum pack newspaper test in Portland, Ore., Apr.-Dec. 1941, 1942 Jan.
      - Duraglas jar label office investigation, 1942 Jan.
      - Memo to: George Dilbert re: differences in consumption of coffee by income classes, 1942 Feb.
      - Vacuum pack in Cook County, Jan.-Dec. 1941, 1942 Feb.
      - Outdoor panel test in Springfield, Mass., Feb.-Dec. 1941, 1942 Feb.
      - Southwestern division posters, July-Dec. 1941, 1942 Feb.
      - Outdoor panel test in Albany, N.Y., Feb.-Dec. 1941, 1942 Feb.
      - Outdoor posting in 3 western cities, Sept.-Dec. 1941, 1942 Feb.
      - Outdoor posting in western cities, Apr.-Dec. 1941, 1942 Feb.
      - Chase & Sanborn vs. Hills Brothers distribution in N.J., 1942 Feb.
      - JWT Consumer Panel, coffee and tea, 1942 June
      - JWT Consumer Panel, coffee and tea, 1942 July
      - Special coffee tests--Mixture 2a558d, 1942 Aug.
      - Special coffee tests--Y vs. P, 1942 Sept.
      - Special coffee tests--N vs. P, 1942 Oct.
      - Estimates of coffee consumption, 1942 Dec.
      - Office survey on rationing, 1943 Mar.
      - Coffee extender check in White Plains and New York (Manhattan), 1943 Apr.
      - Coffee extender check in Chicago and Milwaukee, 1943 Apr.
      - Share of total coffee sales in pounds represented by Maxwell House and Chase & Sanborn--A.C. Nielsen reports, 1943 Oct.
      - JWT Consumer Panel analysis if families buying in leading brands of coffee, first 4 months of 1945, 1945 June
      - Meaning of full coverage audience in Nielsen's radio index, 1945 Dec.
      - Relation of Charlie McCarthy radio program to Chase & Sanborn coffee sales--total pounds--Nov. 1945, 1946 Jan.
      - Memo to: L. Baillis re: Starch rating--Life, Oct. 7, 1946 Dec.
      - Memo to: L. Baillis re: change in Starch ratings, 1946 Dec.
  - R.T. French Co. (vol. 4)
    - Drain cleaners--General information taken from published sources, 1939 Nov.
    - Survey on popularity of week-end meat specials, 1940 Mar.
    - Total sales, 1938-1939, 1940 Apr.
    - Four maps on Atlantis Sales increase and decrease--sales per 1,000 population, 1940 Apr.
    - French's mustard, 6 oz. and 9 oz. size, 1940 May
    - Office test of thick meat sauces--A, B, C, 1940 May
    - Dealer survey on prepared mustard in Jewish sections of N.Y. City, 1940 June
    - Additional information on thick meat sauce, 1940 June
    - Test of Wow tomato juice cocktail--JWT and Atlantis Sales tested, 1940 July
    - Survey of grocery stores in Hartford on prepared puddings, pie fillings, pie crusts; also general information on market situation, 1940 July
    - Information on the potential market for lemon pie fillings, 1940 July
    - Memo to Wm. Resor re: The Good Luck Company, 1940 July
    - Survey of 4 voluntary chain wholesalers in Hartford representing 252 retail outlets on prepared puddings, pie fillings, pie crusts; supplemental information gained in Hartford stores in July survey, 1940 Sept.
    - French's cream salad and Colman's mustard sales, 7 months Jan.-July, 1940 Sept.
    - Dealer survey in New York, Boston, Washington on prepared horseradish mustard, 1940 Oct.
    - Office survey on the use of mustard, New York, 1941 Aug.
    - Memo to Wm. Resor re: Elliott-Haynes surveys on the use of dry mustard, 1941 Sept.
  - General Cigar Company
    - General Cigar Bk. 4